export const SAMPLE_CARD_INFORMATION = [
    [
        {
            "question": "What is a confusion matrix?",
            "answer": "A confusion matrix is a specific table layout that allows visualization of the performance of an algorithm, typically a supervised learning algorithm.",
        },
        {
            "question": "What are false positives?",
            "answer": "False positives are also called type 1 errors.",
        },
        {
            "question": "What are false negatives?",
            "answer": "False negatives are also called type 2 errors.",
        },
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What is a confusion matrix?",
            "answer": "A confusion matrix is a table layout that allows visualization of the performance of a supervised learning algorithm.",
        },
        {
            "question": "What are false positives?",
            "answer": "False positives also referred to as **type 1 error**.",
        },
        {
            "question": "What are false negatives?",
            "answer": "False negatives also referred to as **type 2 error**.",
        },
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What is a confusion matrix?",
            "answer": "Table layout that allows visualization of the performance of a supervised learning algorithm.",
        },
        {
            "question": "What are false positives?",
            "answer": "Type 1 errors.",
        },
        {
            "question": "What are false negatives?",
            "answer": "Type 2 errors.",
        },
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What is a confusion matrix?",
            "answer": "OPTION FOUR BAAYBEEEE",
        },
        {
            "question": "What are false positives?",
            "answer": "OPTION FOUR BAAYBEEEE.",
        },
        {
            "question": "What are false negatives?",
            "answer": "OPTION FOUR BAAYBEEEE.",
        },
    ],
];
